<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
	<title>Jordan Gong&#x27;s Blog - KISS</title>
	<subtitle>A way to show my personal ideas.</subtitle>
	<link href="https://blog.jordangong.com/tags/kiss/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
  <link href="https://blog.jordangong.com"/>
	<generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
	<updated>2020-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://blog.jordangong.com/tags/kiss/atom.xml</id>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>KISS Website Part</title>
		<published>2020-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</published>
		<updated>2020-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<link href="https://blog.jordangong.com/kiss-website-part/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://blog.jordangong.com/kiss-website-part/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Not every personal website can impress me, but most of them that can do this in a bad way.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of them are statically generated websites, posted so-called technical content which has solved well on StackOverflow, or which is not a thing if I read the manuals or other documents developers gave me. But, what I care about now is not the value of content, because there is something worse. When I click on a link direct to that website, it takes forever to load up. I can notice the screen is stuttering while scrolling just like some mining scripts running in the background. Bloated JavaScript is everywhere, doing some fancy stuff, like anime girls in the corner and random geometric animation as a background image.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first time I opened this kind of website, I treated it as a normal one, left it in the background, and continued my works. However, several minutes later, I head the fans of my laptop cranked up, it&#x27;s weird because I was not doing any performance intensive work. Finally, I realized what happened, closed that tab, and everything returned to normal.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used to waste time on picking or writing a stunning template for my website. I added too many useless features and gradually go against my initial thoughts, because I just want to be a cool guy at that time. But now when hosting a content-oriented website, I will keep simple and realistic. If I want to use static website generators, choose simple templates, and make it reading friendly. If I don&#x27;t, just write the website myself, no framework, no JavaScript.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My website is the best place to show my idea. I will post something unique or nothing and share my experience or workaround that I think is meaningful. I will not cater to other&#x27;s favor and post everything in my ways.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
